Jano González

email: info@janogonzalez.com github: janogonzalez

Engineer with 15 years experience in large-scale architectures looking for a SRE role. I've driven large architectural changes focusing on reliability in both team lead and individual contributor positions.

I'm a team player with an honest and respectful communication style who prefers working in cross-functional teams using short delivery cycles.

I enjoy mentoring and public speaking, having presented in conferences like <u>LISA</u>, <u>RubyNation</u> and <u>JRubyConf</u>.

Experience

Production Engineer - SoundCloud

2018 -

- Migrated Memcached infrastructure from bare-metal to Kubernetes.
- Involved in different initiatives for the multi-datacenter migration, for example improving the Chef auto-upload workflow.
- Trained colleagues in the incident response procedure and conducted incident analysis meetings.

Keywords: Kubernetes, Prometheus, Chef, Terraform, MySQL, Memcached, AWS, Linux.

Engineer - SoundCloud

2014 - 2018

- Extracted services, powering SoundCloud's social graph, from a Rails monolith.
- Migrated the monolith from bare-metal to Kubernetes.
- Became the main maintainer of the monolith.

Keywords: Scala, Finagle, Ruby, JRuby, Rails, MySQL, Kubernetes, Memcached, RabbitMQ, Kafka.

CTO – Hopln 2012 – 2013

- Led and recruited the development team.
- Designed and implemented the backend architecture and API.
- Developed and maintained the infrastructure on AWS.

Keywords: Node.js, JavaScript, MySQL, AWS, Linux.

Senior Developer – Continuum	2011
Project Manager – TAISA	2008 – 2010
Systems Analyst – Depósito Central de Valores	2005 – 2008
Consultant – Everis	2005
Research assistant – Universidad del Bío-Bío	2004

Education

Software Engineering – Universidad del Bío-Bío

2000 - 2004

Skills

Teamwork, tech leadership, mentoring, public speaking, monitoring, alerting, incident response, incident analysis, large-scale site architecture.